Guide to the Paul Kwilecki photographs and papers, circa 1910-2008, bulk 1960-2008 RL.00790
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Cemeteries, 1965-1999; 4 folders 67 prints
  - Greenshade Cemetery cleaning, 1977 Apr. (Box PHO 2, Print 22-477-15)
  - Greenshade Cemetery cleaning, 1977 Apr. (Box PHO 2, Print 21-477-5a)
  - Greenshade Cemetery cleaning, 1977 Apr. (Box PHO 2, Print 21-477-22)
  - Cemetery Cleaning/Greenshade Cemetery, 1977 Apr. (Oversize-box 1)
    This text gives a brief description of Greenshade Cemetery and describes a work day and picnic that took place at the cemetery Apr. 30, 1977.
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print 22-1187-3)
    Part of the "Plastic Flowers" series of prints that follows, housed in one folder, 1993.
  - Plastic flowers with hoop, 1993 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 9-1093-10)
  - Broken plastic vase, 1993 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 12-1193-2)
  - Three empty containers, 1993 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 9-1093-12)
  - Recycled champagne cooler, 1993 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 14-1193)
  - Flowers in containers on grave stone, 1993 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 16-1193-13)
  - Flowers in two plastic cups, 1993 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 20-1193)
  - Happy Mother's Day, 1993 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 17-1193)
  - Flowers in cement urn, 1993 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 20-1193)
  - Grave of Alex Vrzal, 1993 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 13-1193)
  - Headless madonna, 1993 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 10-1093-12)
  - Statue of a little devil, 1993 Dec. (Box PHO 3, Print 23-1293-12)
  - Plastic flowers on Granthum grave, 1993 Dec. (Box PHO 3, Print 22-1293)
- County Fairs, 1972-1998; 1 folders 15 prints
  - Man, woman and dog outside sideshow, Decatur County Fair, 1974 Oct. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - A second print of same photo, dated 1976. On the midway, 1976 Oct. [It is unclear which date is correct.] (Box PHO 3, Print 127-1076-10a)
  - Ferris wheel and people, on the midway, Decatur County Fair, 1976 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - Two women and child on the midway, Decatur County Fair, 1974 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - A second print of same photo, 1972 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    According to Kwilecki's caption, this is a duplicate of the previous print, "Two women and child on the midway." It is unclear which date, 1972 or 1974, is correct.
  - Man and woman in tent door, Decatur County Fair, 1977 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 115-1077-33a)
  - Boy and girl on midway, Decatur County Fair, 1977 Oct. (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print 112-1077-5a)
  - Girl with cigarette in booth, Decatur County Fair, 1977 Oct. (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - Decatur County Fair, 1977 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 113-1077-2)
  - Decatur County Fair, 1996 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 32-1096-31)
  - Decatur County Fair, 1996 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 33-1096-12a)
  - Decatur County Fair, 1998 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 50-1098-13a)
  - Decatur County Fair, 1998 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 51-1098-13a)
  - No known title, 1968 (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - No known title, undated (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
- Battle's Quarters, 1961-1971; 1 folders 15 prints
  [See also Oversize Box 1.]
  - Street in Battle's Quarters, children playing, 1970 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    This is the one dirt street comprising the quarters. Children play in it. Originally built to house workers at Battle's Lumber Co., it outlived its original purpose by forty years. It was a terrible slum. It has been torn down.
  - Man without shirt and woman on porch, Battle's Quarters, 1971 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    The houses were impossible to heat in winter, cool in summer, or otherwise made comfortable. Consequently, most life was lived on the porches and in the yards. The man at right is the Quarter’s stud, and this is one of his girl friends.
  - Back porch, Battle's Quarters, two women and two children, 1971 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    Behind the house doing the washing.
  - Girl with Afro sitting on bumper of old car, 1970 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    A child of the quarters sitting on an abandoned car parked between two of the houses.
  - Battle's Quarters, woman slicing onions outside her house, 1970 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - Battle's Quarters, woman and washtub with children in background, 1970 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    Woman doing the washing on a cold winter day.
  - View of street in Battle's Quarters with four girls in the foreground, 1971 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - Woman on porch looking in mirror, 1971 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - Family assembled on front porch, 1971 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    All these people lived in this one house. There was no indoor plumbing.
  - Woman leaning on her porch railing, 1971 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - Man and woman on front porch talking, child in screen door, 1971 (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    In summer life was mostly lived outdoors.
  - Three women in yard, 1971 (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    Saturday afternoon.
  - White dress in rain, 1961 (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - Man in doorway, baby on porch floor, circa 1971 [matted] (Oversize-box 1, Print unnumbered)
    I have observed elsewhere that life in the quarters was lived mostly out of doors. To demonstrate how true that is, this man was making love to a woman just inside the open door when he saw me about to photograph his child on the porch. He is in the process of dressing himself as he looks dauntingly at me.
  - Two men and women seated, 1970 [matted] (Oversize-box 1, Print unnumbered)
    Saturday afternoon and everyone sits around in the shade and talks. These three were totally unconcerned with my photography. I had to interrupt them to ask them to look my way.
- Bainbridge, Georgia, 1965-2001; 3 folders 48 prints
  - Woman in back seat of car on Water Street, 1965 (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    Scene on Water Street.
  - Water Street, 1996 Jan. (Box PHO 3, Print 43-196-231)
  - Water at Broad Street, 1996 Sept. (Box PHO 3, Print 28-996-24)
  - Residence, 1996 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 43-1196-11)
  - Residence, 1996 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 45-1196-11a)
  - Residence, 1996 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 40-1196-10a)
  - Residence, 1996 Nov. (Box PHO 3, Print 41-1196-30)
  - Cox Funeral Home, 1996 Oct. (Box PHO 3, Print 34-1096-26)
  - No known title, 1996 October? (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - Residence, 1996 Dec. (Box PHO 3, Print 49-1296-20)
  - Dawn on Broad Street, 1996 Sept. (Box PHO 3, Print 25-996-5a)
  - Centennial Field, 1996 Sept. (Box PHO 3, Print 30-996-27)
  - Flint River Mills, Inc., 1996 Jan. (Box PHO 3, Print 4-196-2)
  - One block of Water Street, 1979 Feb. (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print 28-279)
    View down Water Street on a Sunday morning.
  - Three city workers, 1976 Sept. (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print 118-976)
    City workers repairing street.
  - Modern architecture, 1980 Sept. (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print 84-980-1)
  - Dead cat in front of house, 1978 May (Box PHO 3, Print 37-578-9)
    The image speaks for itself.
  - The old Memorial Bridge in early morning fog, 1973 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    Just before it was replaced.
  - Truck salvage yard, 1989 Mar. (Box PHO 3, Print 24-389)
  - Truck salvage yard, 1989 Mar. (Box PHO 3, Print 20-389-10)
  - Restored water fountain on corner of Willis Park, 1987 June (Box PHO 3, Print 3-687-8)
  - Night view of North Broad Street, 1972 (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
  - Court house, 1979 Dec. (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print 174-1279-19)
    View of the top of the court house tower, seen from behind the Bon Air Hotel.
  - Graduation at Bainbridge Junior College (now called Bainbridge College), 1978 June ( Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print 45-678-20)
  - Shanty and chicken coop, West Bainbridge, 1977 (Understandings) (Box PHO 3, Print unnumbered)
    Once a typical house in a ghetto section of West Bainbridge, but now torn down. I don't know why I included it in Understandings.
  - Florida Seafood Company, 1978 Oct. (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print 88-1078-7)
    Reflected in the window is the Court House. This photo could also be used in the Court House series.
  - Industry: City water tank with Lynch's water tank, seen from the Pear Orchard, 1991 Oct. (Box PHO 4, Print 70-1091-11)
  - Blind couple walking down West Street, 1965 (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print unnumbered)
    His name was Steve Dickinson, I think.
  - Walter Floyd's front porch (on Broad Street), 1979 Jan. (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print 12-179)
  - City Hall, 1980 Feb. (Box PHO 4, Print 9-280-7)
    Formerly First State National Bank, it was purchased by the city for City Hall in the early 1970s.
  - Man and wife eating ice cream. Bainbridge Mall, 1976 Apr. (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print 476-2)
  - Shotwell Street at Christmas, 1997 Nov. (Box PHO 4, Print 41-1197-25)
  - Preparing for graduation, Centennial Field, 1999 Sept. (Box PHO 4, Print 10-999-10a)
  - Martin Luther King Day parade, 2000 Dec. (Box PHO 4, Print 1-120-12a)
  - Martin Luther King Day parade (duplicate), 2000 Dec. (Box PHO 4, Print 1-120-12a)
  - Expressway, 2000 Dec. (Box PHO 4, Print 1-120-23a)
  - Expressway (duplicate), 2000 Dec. (Box PHO 4, Print 1-120-23a)
  - Independence Street, 1991 Oct. (Box PHO 4, Print 70-1091-11)
  - The Bon Air at Christmas, 2001 Dec. (Box PHO 4, Print 26-12-01-23A)
  - Corner of West and Market Street, Bainbridge, 1998 Oct. (Box PHO 4, Print 49-1098-8)
  - No known title, 1978 (Box PHO 28, Print 27-378-17)
  - No known title, 1977 (Box PHO 28, Print 48-677-5)
  - No known title, 1997 (Box PHO 28, Print 3-197-32)
  - No known title, 1981? (Box PHO 28, Print 29-281)
  - No known title, undated (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - Short order restaurant on North Broad Street at night, 1970 [matted] (Oversize-box 1, Print unnumbered)
  - Broad Street on Sunday morning, 1980 June (Oversize-box 1, Print 62-680-22)
  - North Broad Street, 1980 Aug. (Understandings) (Oversize-box 1, Print 82-880-10)
  - Interior of pool hall on North Broad Street owned and operated by Ertha Lee Coney, 1981 Apr. (Oversize-box 1, Print 45-481-8)
- Agriculture, 1996; 1 folders 1 print
  - Grain storage, 1996 Feb. (Box PHO 4, Print 9-296-8)
- Flint River, Georgia, 1977-1992; 2 folders 31 prints
  - People swimming at Boat Basin Beach, 1992 July (Box PHO 4, Print 10-792-14)
  - People swimming at Boat Basin Beach, 1992 July (Box PHO 4, Print 10-792-16)
  - Couple at Boat Basin Beach, 1992 June (Box PHO 4, Print 4-692-20a)
  - Mother and child at Boat Basin Beach, 1992 June (Box PHO 4, Print 3-692-28)
  - No known title, 1992 June (Box PHO 28, Print 3-692-33)
  - Girl standing in water at Boat Basin Beach, 1992 July (Box PHO 4, Print 6-792-30)
  - Three boys on lifeguard stand and swimmers, boat basin, 1979 June ( Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print 77-679-19a)
  - Man and wife fishing on riverbank, 1979 June (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print 82-679-27a)
  - Woman fishing under highway bridge, 1979 Sept. (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print 117-979-15)
  - Swimming at Boat Basin Beach, 1992 July (Box PHO 4, Print 7-792-23)
  - Nature's own cyclorama, the Flood of '94, Flint River, 1994 July (Box PHO 4, Print 18-794-11)
  - Woman in housecoat fishing at Flint River, 1979 June (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print 87-679-29a)
  - Couple fishing on tubs, Flint River, 1980 Apr. (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print 37-480-24a)
    Two people fishing: big can/little can.
  - Couple with baby at Boat Basin Beach, 1989 July (Box PHO 4, Print 30-789-21)
    Swimming at a 'beach' the city created at one end of the boat basin, Flint River.
  - View of the Flint River from bank, 1990 Feb. (Box PHO 4, Print 5-290-5)
  - Dismantling Memorial Bridge, man climbing ladder, 1977 (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print unnumbered)
    Dismantling of old Memorial Bridge after new bridge was completed. I have a whole set of pictures documenting its taking down.
  - Woman preparing to fish in the river, 1979 June (Understandings) (Box PHO 4, Print 78-679-27a)
  - Flint River, 1990 Jan. (Box PHO 4, Print 1-190-16)
    Scene in early morning fog on the river bank.
  - Family out for a swim at Boat Basin Beach, 1989 July (Box PHO 4, Print 33-789-11)
    If this is the typical American family, God help us!
  - Having fun. Man and girlfriend, Boat Basin Beach, 1989 Aug. (Box PHO 4, Print 35-889-26)
  - View looking south towards state docks, 1979 May (Box PHO 4, Print 62-579)
  - Fishing, 1980 Mar. (Box PHO 4, Print LB 777-54)
  - Two swimming couples, 1981 June (Box PHO 4, Print 78-681-10)
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - No known title, 1979 May (Box PHO 28, Print 69-579)
  - No known title, 1979 May (Box PHO 28, Print 72-579)
  - A family and their vehicle picnicking by the river, 1979 May (Oversize-box 1, Print 68-579)
  - Runner warming up before race at springtime festival, 1978 Apr. (Oversize-box 1, Print 37-578-24a)
  - A yearly festival used to be held on the banks of the Flint to celebrate spring, 1980 May (Oversize-box 1, Print 54-580-15)
  - Man, baby, wife with inner tube at Boat Basin Beach, 1981 May (Oversize-box 1, Print 77-581-7)
  - Boys under sign at Boat Basin Beach, 1981 June (Oversize-box 1, Print 81-681-11)
- Houses, 1961-1985; 1 folders 26 prints
  - The Patterson-Powell-McDuffie residence on Broughton St., 1985 Oct. (Box PHO 5, Print 41-1085)
  - Typical old farm house abandoned, 1982 June (Box PHO 5, Print 59-682-8)
    Some are left to collapse; this one burned about a year after this picture was made.
  - Typical abandoned farm house out in the county, 1984 Nov. (Box PHO 5, Print 64-1184-12)
    As the small farmer leaves the farm, his houses are left behind.
  - A once decent farm house, now abandoned, 1989 Oct. (Box PHO 5, Print 48-1089-18)
    Dating from the last century.
  - Another view of the house shown (1989 Oct.), 1988 Dec. (Box PHO 5, Print 7-1288)
  - Living room of the Clark Gurley house, 1975 Mar. 22 (Box PHO 5, Print unnumbered)
    The house is now torn down.
  - The home of Elinor Curry, the last of an old Decatur County family, 1988 Dec. (Box PHO 5, Print 5-1288-4)
  - This was the oldest house in Decatur County, 1976 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 114-876)
    It was on the corner of Broughton and Clay Streets. My grandfather stayed there for a short time when he came to Bainbridge in 1869. It was torn down shortly after this picture was made.
  - Shelf in the home of Mr. And Mrs. J. M. Thompson. Decatur County, 1965 (Box PHO 5, Print unnumbered)
  - Showing typical Christmas decorations on a Negro house, 1980 Dec. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 5, Print 121-1280-7)
  - Interior of shanty, 1961 (Box PHO 5, Print unnumbered)
  - Typical old farm house, 1984 Oct. (Box PHO 5, Print 59-1084-3)
  - No known title, 1985 October (Box PHO 28, Print 44-1085-7)
  - Dismantling a house, home to four generations, 1987 July (Box PHO 5, Print 7-787)
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - No known title, 1979 March (Box PHO 28, Print 36-379)
  - No known title, 1980 February (Box PHO 28, Print 17-280-8)
  - No known title, 1986 June (Box PHO 28, Print 12-686-12)
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - A residence, Bainbridge, GA, 1979 March (Box PHO 28, Print 35-379)
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - 1965. Beecher Thomas and wife in living room. [matted] (Oversize-box 1, Print unnumbered)
    Interior of the home of Mr. and Mrs. Beecher Thomas on Shotwell and Scott Streets.
  - Interior of Gus Poulas residence, circa 1969 [matted] (Oversize-box 1, Print unnumbered)
    This boy rented a room from Gus. This photograph was purchased by the Museum of Modern Art many years ago.
- Landscapes, 1982-1991; 1 folders 9 prints
  - Hogs and drain pond, 1989 Feb. (Box PHO 5, Print 17-289-13)
    This is a familiar sight in Decatur County where livestock is a major crop.
  - Typical swamp in southeast part of county, 1990 Feb. (Box PHO 5, Print 3-290-11)
  - Swamp around Attapulgus Creek, 1982 Jan. (Box PHO 5, Print 7-182-2)
  - Cypress trees in Lake Douglas, 1991 Mar. (Box PHO 5, Print 4-391)
  - The banks of Spring Creek north of Brinson, 1985 Mar. (Box PHO 5, Print 10-385)
  - No title known, 1984 November (Box PHO 28, Print 61-1184-8)
  - Scenes of Decatur County, 1989 July (Box PHO 5, Print 31-789-6)
  - Scenes: the old Atlantic Coast Line trestle across the Flint River, looking east, 1991 Oct. (Box PHO 5, Print 67-1091-30)
    Early morning.
  - Woods reclaiming their territory. Decatur County, 1989 Nov. (Box PHO 5, Print 58-1189-14)
- Laura Pope, 1984 March; 1 folders 4 prints
  - Laura Pope, 1984 Mar. (Box PHO 5, Print 16-384)
    These statues were constructed during and shortly after World War I by a genuine eccentric in Grady County named Laura Pope. At one time there were over a hundred such life-size statues standing in the yard. All were of soldiers or nurses or spirits. She made life-masks for the faces and concrete for the bodies, which were stylized and awkwardly rendered.
  - Laura Pope, 1984 Mar. (Box PHO 5, Print 18-384)
  - Laura Pope, 1984 Mar. (Box PHO 5, Print 16-384)
    When she died the farm was sold to Buster Nixon who tried to conserve the statues, but rain and freezing temperatures cracked much of the concrete.
  - Laura Pope, 1984 Mar. (Box PHO 5, Print 16-384)
- Pear Orchard, 1961, 1971; 1 folders 2 prints
  - Woman with cat in doorway, Pear Orchard, 1961 (Box PHO 6, Print No#)
    This was one of the first pictures I made that satisfied me.
  - Three boys with basketball, 1971 (Box PHO 6, Print unnumbered)
    Children were playing basketball and asked to have their picture made.
- Industry, 1981-1992; 4 folders 46 prints
  - Chemical Plant, 1991 Aug. (Box PHO 4, Print 40-891-22)
    Tower and warehouse. Vigaro plant. Bainbridge.
  - Worker at her machine. Elberta Crate and Box Co. Bainbridge, 1981 Nov. (Box PHO 4, Print 134-1181-7)
  - Flint River Mills. Bainbridge, 1991 June (Box PHO 4, Print 17-691-2)
  - Machine operator watching computer controlled lathe mill steel block, 1991 July (Box PHO 4, Print 35-791-11)
    Time required: 12 minutes. Time formerly required: 6 hours. Lynch Machine Co. Bainbridge.
  - Columbia Peanut Co., 1991 July (Box PHO 4, Print 23-791)
  - Decatur Cotton Gin, 1991 Oct. (Box PHO 4, Print 70-1091-28)
    Mysterious landscape? No. Discharge of cotton dust that has flocked the landscape. The planet-like object is a mote of cotton dust that got on my lens.
  - The log yard of Elberta Crate and Box Co. seen early morning in fog, 1991 Oct. (Box PHO 4, Print 67-1091-23a)
  - Pulpwood worker in the woods felling trees. Decatur County, Ga., 1990 May (Box PHO 4, Print 10-590-14)
  - Repair man in the dark recesses of Flint River Mills. Bainbridge, 1991 July (Box PHO 4, Print 27-791-15)
  - Worker operating bagging machine. Flint River Mills. Bainbridge, 1991 July (Box PHO 4, Print 24-791-4)
    He is wearing goggles and mask because of the grain dust in the air.
  - Clean-up man sweeping, Elberta Crate and Box Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Oct. (Box PHO 4, Print unnumbered)
  - Logger in his truck in woods. Decatur County, Ga. (Pulpwood), 1990 May (Box PHO 4, Print 9-590-6)
  - Worker atop rail car loading corn from storage tanks, 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 4, Print 62-991-28a)
    Dust and trash are being sucked off at lower right. Dollar Farm Products Co. Bainbridge.
  - The break room at Elberta Crate and Box Co., 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 4, Print 58-991-10)
  - Worker signalling for more logs. Elberta Crate and Box. Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 4, Print 61-991-8)
  - An agri-business structure. Peanut warehouse. Columbia Peanut Co., 1991 June (Box PHO 4, Print 15-691-1)
  - An agri-business structure. Dollar Farm Products Co., 1989 Aug. (Box PHO 4, Print 42-889-7)
  - An agri-business structure. Columbia Peanut Co., 1991 June (Box PHO 4, Print 16-691-12)
  - Water towers. Lynch Machine/Miller Hydro Co., 1991 July (Box PHO 4, Print 34-791-14)
  - Seldom used machine relegated to a dark corner of Lynch Machine Co., but handsome in its purposefulness, 1991 July (Box PHO 4, Print 31-791-25)
  - Flint River Mills, Bainbridge, 1991 June (Box PHO 4, Print 19-691)
    Is this a building or an outdoor machine? A sculpture?
  - Pulpwood truck, 1984 Sept. (Box PHO 4, Print 53-984-10)
  - Machine operator watching computer controlled lathe, 1991 July (Box PHO 5, Print 30-791-19)
    This is new: seeing workers sitting staring at machines. Lynch Machine Co.
  - Worker preparing to weld. Southeastern Minerals Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Aug. (Box PHO 5, Print 50-891-28)
  - Worker in pit preparing to weld. Southeastern Minerals Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Aug. (Box PHO 5, Print 41-891-15)
  - Workers assembling shute [sic] for tower. Southeastern Minerals Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Aug. (Box PHO 5, Print 46-891-17a)
  - Man emerging from pit. Southeastern Minerals Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Aug. (Box PHO 5, Print 42-891-23)
  - Man lowering platter onto turntable of glass molding machine, 1991 Oct. (Box PHO 5, Print 66-1091-31)
    Behind him can be seen the largest machine yet built. Lynch Machine Co.
  - Worker at State Dock, 1992 July (Box PHO 5, Print 10-792-26)
  - Worker on production line at Southeastern Minerals Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 64-991-26)
  - Pulpwood worker standing beside his loaded truck in the woods. Decatur County, 1990 May (Box PHO 5, Print 10-590-3)
  - Woman ironing new made pants. Williamson-Dickie, Bainbridge, 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 53-991-24)
  - Worker making pants at Williamson-Dickie Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 51-991-13)
  - Worker ironing new made work pants at Williamson-Dickie. Bainbridge, 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 53-991-17)
  - Seven day old baby at Williamson-Dickie Manufacturing Co., 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 57-991-19)
  - Worker on break. Williamson-Dickie Mfg. Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 55-991-23)
  - Three women, Williamson-Dickie Manufacturing Co., 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 55-991-15)
  - Break, Williamson-Dickie Manufacturing Co., 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 52-991-31)
  - Worker, Williamson-Dickie plant. Bainbridge, 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 52-991-17)
  - Agri-business building. Dollar Farm Products Co., 1991 June (Box PHO 5, Print 13-691-7)
  - Agri-business. Columbia Peanut Co. seen from Dollar Farm Products Co., 1990 (Box PHO 5, Print unnumbered)
    This is what a peanut operation looks like from across the road.
  - Agri-business. Columbia Peanut Co. seen from Dollar Farm Products Co., 1985 August (Box PHO 28, Print 40-885)
  - Cotton gin worker wearing safety glass and ear plugs for noise protection. Decatur Gin Co., 1991 Sept. (Box PHO 5, Print 63-991-5)
  - Worker on bagging line at Flint River Mills. Bainbridge, 1991 July (Box PHO 5, Print 35-791-24)
  - Men preparing to hoist tower head into position sixty feet up. Southeastern Minerals Co. Bainbridge, 1991 Aug. (Box PHO 5, Print 48-891-23)
  - Worker holding hoist strap. Southeastern Minerals. Bainbridge, 1981 Aug. (Box PHO 5, Print 46-891-24a)
- Shade Tobacco, 1962-1982 and undated; 2 folders 21 prints
  - Putting up the shades, 1962 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    This was one of the earliest pictures I made that pleased me. Even so the exposure leaves something to be desired.
  - Woman sitting in front of tobacco shack, 1963 (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    Typical tobacco shack in which workers lived. Woman is trying to get warm in the sunshine.
  - Front porch of two-family tobacco tenant house, 1964 (Understandings) (Box PHO 8, Print unnumbered)
    A duplex shack in which two families live. Shade tobacco is used as the wrapper for cigars. The leaf has to be absolutely perfect.